Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his trials, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
The elves reborn as Golden Dawn mages descended upon the castle.
Meanwhile, the Eye of the Midnight Sun's base arrived at the capital, carrying Licht and Raya.
Who the hell thought it'd be a good idea to invite the giant floating boulder to the party?
But look, a pretty little birdie just showed up too.
Nozel and Noelle met up with Yami's group for a brief moment.
Then all the knights went their separate ways in order to protect the people of the Clover Kingdom.
However, when the Silvers returned to their childhood residence, they were forced to contend with the enemy's devastating compass magic.
Just when all seemed lost, Noelle combined everything she'd learned from her training and experience as a member of the Black Bulls with her resolute desire to rescue her siblings, and gained an awe-inspiring new power.
I'll crush you and this world you've made!
Let's go!
Let's go, 22 yamance!
Let's go, 22 yamance, 22 yamance!
I'll crush you and this world you've made!
I need to keep working Disney!
Agora יה whipping dire o que jimase into Centre,
最 열심히 sonatural territory!
Let's not
That's all we have now
Even if you're doing except you You want to break your body
Don't lose sight
So what we he doing?!
jetzt
I'll will do the Sunday as it stays
If now,
it will be
Philip
Blow it away and it comes right back
Human magic. It's so impertinent.
They've invaded the third level and the inner courtyard too.
So the safest and therefore loveliest route is...
That way.
Everyone, please hurry outside!
We're so lucky you arrived in time.
Yes, you saved us!
Well, this is the esteemed Vermillion residence after all.
Which means the terrain is completely in our favor.
And look!
My beautiful cherry blossom magic confuses the enemy while concealing our allies' whereabouts.
Plus, the fungus magic secreted by those shriveled spores helps to muddle any attempts to locate us.
And of course, my sister Mimosa is using her plant magic to survey the surroundings and guide our path.
All of our enchanting techniques are perfectly suited to evacuation and with no violence necessary.
How gorgeous!
Would you please stop talking before you blow our cover, you loudmouthed buffoon?
They're only our enemies because they're possessed by elf spirits.
Deep down, they're still our squad mates.
I swear we'll do everything possible to bring them back to normal.
Hey there. Working hard, huh?
David!
Nope. Sorry, my name's Babel.
I didn't notice his presence at all.
If he found us, that must mean our spells aren't working.
Relax! Why do you guys look so angry?
Sorry for barging in, but all I wanted to do was track you guys down and say a quick hello.
If I was trying to kill you, then you would already be dead, so there's no reason to get all defensive.
I don't think that's all he wants.
Tell us what you're really after, elf!
Oh, not much.
But I can catch you up on the details.
If you haven't figured it out, my friends and I have been reincarnated with much stronger magic than you possess.
And now we've come here to pay the royals a visit.
You can sense it too, right?
You know, the fact that something even more powerful is heading over here as we speak.
Not much point evacuating the castle.
Either way, you're all going to die.
So you might as well surrender at this point.
I'm pretty formidable, but the rest of us are tough as well.
Man, this takes me back.
I can't wait to see everybody.
I won't let you hurt anyone else.
We'll defeat you no matter what!
I do admire your determination, but it's too late now.
Once we take care of your king, this invasion's as good as over with.
We sent one of our most qualified people to deal with him too.
Believe me, the guy's as stubborn as he is twisted.
King Clover's trapped like a rat.
Oh, and...
Our guy has something particularly nasty up his sleeve.
Perfect magic for killing a king.
I don't have what it takes to stop that spell.
How's he this powerful?
In great!
How dare you come in here and disgrace this sacred hall!
Longris, dear!
What's wrong?
This is the current king.
He looks so seedy.
What?!
I will not abide such disrespect in my royal presence!
You should be ashamed to have this traitorous rebel for a son!
Please, sir.
This has to be a misunderstanding.
Yes, something's wrong!
Our precious son, Longris, would never betray the Clover Kingdom!
Silence!
With all of our defenses outside, how could that scoundrel have weaseled his way in here?
I swear, Julius and the other magic knights are positively useless!
You have left me no choice!
Now I'll show you my magic!
Here!
Behold the magnificent talent of a king!
I see you're too busy trembling to escape!
My knight's magic!
Absolute monarch of divine brilliance!
What say you?
Positively godlike, is it not?
Bow down and grovel before my royal visage!
What?!
What did you do?!
How sad.
That spell was ridiculously sluggish.
I won't kill you just yet.
Let's start with your legs.
No, wait!
Longris!
You can't do this! You know it's not right!
If you go through with it, you and a lot of other people will be hurt!
People who care about you very much!
So, please!
Shut your mouth!
Your kind killed the elves, and you have the nerve to talk about being hurt?
Longris, no!
No!
Please tell me he didn't injure you, Miss Finnis.
No, I'm fine.
Finral's here.
I'm sorry, who are you?
Your brother! Wake up!
Stop trying to act like a hero, Finral!
Haha, I wasn't though, really!
How'd they manage to get past our forces?
Oh, those other glowing guys?
Yeah, we took care of them already.
But it would've gone a lot faster if Skinny here had been on the ball.
Excuse me, you were the one goofing around the whole time!
Freaking meathead!
Keke! You shouldn't have split up your forces, elf boy!
Because you don't stand a chance against us on your own!
I'm not worried.
Care to explain how you overpowered that many by yourselves?
Why don't we show ya?
You can't counter this.
It's too late!
I'm sorry, I should've warned you before.
The spell I'm using retaliates automatically.
Give me a challenge, would you? I'm bored.
We can do that!
His abilities are unbelievable.
There's no special mage in the whole kingdom who can cancel out a spell like that.
It's an extremely protective shield, and he can keep it going constantly.
Father, Miss Finnis, you should run away and let us deal with this.
You fool! You're merely a transport for the Black Bulls. You can't defeat him!
I may not be able to do any damage.
And he may be the vice-captain of the Golden Dawn.
But all that matters to me right now is that Longris and I are brothers!
He's lost his mind.
Don't you go underestimating my wheels, mister.
What? But I…
Look, pal, you're in the way. I'll throw you in there myself.
Oh, Longris! My precious Longris!
Alright, you're going in there with him.
Longris!
I'm worried, Finral. Promise me you'll come back alive.
Sure. And I'll bring Longris with me.
WEEEEEEET!
I SHOULD BE FIRST PRIORITY!
Huh? Oh.
Honestly, you're such a useless lo-
What's the hurry?
You should stick around. I was just getting ready to mutilate His Majesty.
I won't let you.
Care, care! This kid talks a big game!
I'll cut him down to size!
Peppering magic! Death's Scythe!
Lunatic Slash!
You moronic hacker!
That's one way to save someone.
He's the king, you know.
Care, care! You interfered with my slashes!
Not too shabby, pal!
Never mind. He's already moved on.
Huh. Still think you can hold a candle to my strength?
It's time for you, filth, to learn your place!
Sure.
He can use his attack spells without turning off that defensive shield?
Not gonna fight fair, are ya?
If this spell hits you even one time, you'll be dead.
Spatial magic?
Spatial magic.
Archangels crash!
Fallen angels wing-meat!
The difference in our power is too great!
I can only block about half of these things!
Avoid them however you can!
Nah!
Hey, who said you could start bargain orders?
Dark magic!
Black hole!
Kit-kit!
Reinforcement magic!
Leg strength boost!
Dark magic!
Dark cloak!
Light look!
Slap!
Yami!
Thanks for that.
If we wanna land even a scratch on this guy, we're gonna have to do something about that barrier.
But he's constantly throwing his orbs at us, and Finral's magic can only cancel out so many of them.
A long battle puts us at a disadvantage, so we need to end this thing nice and quick.
Which means...
It'll take more than one of us attacking him at the same time.
I can cover this side myself.
I haven't had prey like this in a while!
Ooh, I want to slice him up so bad!
You're mine now!
Using his instinctual ability to transform the very nature of his magic, Jack's ferocious blades are able to cut through practically any type of spell.
All because his desire to slash things is so intense.
Here you go!
Even though spatial magic has unique properties of its own, he can cut his way through it just the same.
But how?
Well, well. That scrawny psycho came in handy after all.
Suffering magic?
Now, dark magic!
Dark cloaked!
Ready, Jack?
Ready!
Dead side!
Slash!
Can't, can't, can't!
Alright!
Damn.
I was surprised when they eliminated my shield.
But they're still one step behind!
Looks like your spatial magic is worthless for attacking AND defending!
My power can't actually defeat anybody.
But...
I'll send you to oblivion!
Spatial magic!
Fallen Angel's Wingbeat!
What the...
He dropped his guard so he could transport them?
My Fallen Angel's Wingbeat can forcibly transport a person from one location to another.
I'm gonna save my friends!
And you too!
Well, I hate to break it to you, human.
You're fast!
But I'm just a little bit faster!
I'll kill all of you in one go!
It's fine.
These guys are Magic Knight Captains.
If anyone can win this fight, it's them!
The more I use them, the quicker my blades become!
Alright, kid.
Time for a nap!
I've got just the thing!
My Dark Magic Dark Cloak Lightless Blunt Strike!
That should work!
How could you beat me?
When you're just...
HUMAN TRASH!
I hate your kind!
All of you are so filthy, petty and repulsive!
Just disappear!
I don't care!
He finally lost the rest of his marbles!
This mana...
It feels even more sinister than it did earlier.
Great!
What the hell are we supposed to do with them now?
Nothing.
It's over at this point.
He's too far gone.
My magic is so insignificant compared to his, he won't even notice it.
Longris!
When I think about it, we never actually argued.
Not since we were children.
I always ran away instead.
Using my lack of talent as an excuse.
Even though I'm the older brother.
And I knew how lonely you were feeling.
This is...
My last chance.
Your big brother really shines when it comes to speed and accuracy.
So I'll stop you!
Whatever it takes!
I hope you're ready!
Wake up!
Longris!
Listen to me!
For being the gifted younger brother, you're kind of a handful, aren't you?
Sorry it took so long.
I'm not really good at this stuff.
Come with me.
.
Oh...
Listen to me!
For being the gifted younger brother, you're kind of a handful, aren't you?
Sorry it took so long. I'm not really good at this stuff.
Come with me.
That's real cute. We do all the grunt work and you save the day with your brotherly love.
Good job, Venral. You did it.
But the big question is, what's their endgame here? Just wipe out humanity and call it a day?
No. I think they've got something else up their sleeve.
It won't be long now, Licht. Soon I'll get to see you awake.
Did the two of you just get here as well?
Who's he, brother? That isn't Licht.
You're Potri. I know that you always look tough to Licht, but now you've copied his appearance and everything?
What do you mean, copied him? It wasn't my choice. I was in this body when I awoke. I suppose you could call it my destiny.
Wow. That's creepy.
Hey.
Droid. It's been a long time, hasn't it?
I was just awakened, actually. So it doesn't feel like it's been very long to me.
Ha ha ha ha! Good point.
And how are you, little Eklot?
Hello, sir.
Raya, where is Licht right now?
Oh. Potri's here too, huh? Licht's using a fake body.
So it's either because of that or because he's the one who activated the Forbidden Reincarnation spell.
But his memories haven't completely come back yet, so he's asleep.
How unfortunate.
Well, anyway, it's good to see the gang's all here, finally.
The others are out back.
That's true.
And I'm fairly certain the Golden Dawn has taken care of eradicating the humans in our absence.
Judging by that large hole in the castle, I'd say Lotri must have overindulged,
and I'm sure that pompous king is long dead.
Now all that's left is to fit the final magic stone into the pedestal within the castle
and initiate the spell that will destroy the Clover Kingdom.
The magic stone is already in our hands.
We'll wash away the malice brought on by that forbidden spell,
and then our reincarnation will be truly complete.
After humanity is snuffed out,
we will reclaim this world, making it a peaceful place for elves alone.
I don't know who's in there,
but I'm guessing it won't be an easy fight.
Wonder what my dumbass subordinates and the other magic knights are doing.
At this rate, I'll have to flatten every one of those elves by myself.
Now, I'll slash them first.
Keep dreaming.
I'll slash them first.
Women's
CLOTHES Are Clips
Me!
At this rate, I'll have to flatten every one of those elves by myself.
Now I'll slash them first.
Keep dreaming.
They're mine.
Hey! I just said I'm the one who's gonna kick their asses.
The only person kicking ass will be me!
No, me!
Me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, you sure piss me off.
Stop copying me, weirdo.
I said stop copying me right now.
Hey, what's going on here?
We're doing everything the same way.
In essence, Yami and Jack are basically the same person.
No, we're not.
My beautiful voice, my beautiful flowers, everything about me, Kier's beautiful vermilion is beautiful.
Black Clover, page 110, the Raging Bull joins the showdown.
I'm not a Raging Bull, I'm just ragingly beautiful.